Guide to the Leonard Jimmie Savage Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Addresses and Writings, Series III; 5 linear feet (13 boxes)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, corrections (Box 46, Folder 147)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, distribution lists (Box 46, Folder 148)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, reviews (Box 46, Folder 149)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, hardback copy (Box 46, Folder 150)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, chapters 1-5 (1960 Aug 28 version) (Box 46, Folder 151-152)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, chapters 1-6 (1960 Aug 28 version) (Box 46, Folder 153)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, chapter 6, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 154)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, chapters 2, 4, 5, 6, 12 (1962 Jul version) (Box 47, Folder 155)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, chapter 3 (1962 Sep version) (Box 47, Folder 156)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, chapters 3, 7 (1962 Nov version) (Box 47, Folder 157)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, chapters 7-10 (1962 Dec version) (Box 47, Folder 158)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, chapters 1-5 (1963 Apr master copy) (Box 47, Folder 159)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, chapters 6-12 (1963 Apr master copy) (Box 47, Folder 160)
  - How To Gamble If You Must (1963 Apr version) (Box 47, Folder 161)
  - How To Gamble If You Must (1963 Apr version) (Box 48, Folder 162)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, chapters 1-5 (revision of 1963 Apr version) (Box 48, Folder 163)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, chapters 6-12 (revision of 1963 Apr Version) (Box 48, Folder 164)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, chapters 1-5 (working manuscripts marked "obsolete--1964 Jul 31") (Box 48, Folder 165)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, chapters 6-12 (working mss. marked "obsolete--1964 Jul 31") (Box 48, Folder 166)
  - How To Gamble If You Must, galley proofs (Box 49, Folder 167-169)
  - reviews by Savage for Mathematical Reviews (from volumes 11-17) (Box 49A, Folder 170)
  - reviews by Savage for Mathematical Reviews (from volumes 19-24, 32-36, 38) (Box 49A, Folder 171)
  - reviews by Savage for Mathematical Reviews (from volumes 39-43) (Box 49A, Folder 172)
  - reviews from Mathematical Reviews of books and papers by Savage (Box 49A, Folder 173)
  - review by Savage for American Statistical Association Journal, v.50, 1955 December (Box 49A, Folder 174)
  - list of reviews prepared by Savage for Mathematical Reviews, undated (Box 49A, Folder 175)
  - bibliography of L. J. Savage (revised as of 1973 Jul 29) (Box 49A, Folder 176)
  - dedication to L. J. Savage by Fienberg and Zellner in Studies in Bayesian Econometrics and Statistics, 1975 (Box 49A, Folder 177)
  - reprints of articles by others (Box 49A, Folder 178)
  - Charts for How To Gamble If You Must (Box 75)
- Teaching Materials and Notes, Series IV; 3 linear feet (6 boxes)
  General note
  (lecture notes on statistics)
  The materials in this series are arranged chronologically. Filed at the end of this series are research notes by Savage on various books, articles, and topics.
  - 1947 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - 1947 (Box 50, Folder 2-3)
  - 1948-1952 (Box 50, Folder 4-7)
  - 1953-1957 (Box 51, Folder 8-14)
  - 1958-1964 (Box 52, Folder 15-22)
  - 1965-1967 (Box 53, Folder 23-28)
  - 1968-1969 (Box 54, Folder 29-34)
  - 1970-1971, undated (Box 55, Folder 35-38)
  - misc. Savage teaching materials (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - misc. teaching materials by others (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - research notes by Savage, 1946, 1949, 1954-1955, 1957, 1959-1960, 1962 (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - research notes by Savage, undated (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - notes by Savage on books and articles, 1946, 1950-1951, 1954-1956, 1958-1959 (Box 56, Folder 43)
  - notes by Savage on books and articles, 1960-1963, 1966-1967, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 44)
  - notes by Savage on books and articles, undated (Box 56, Folder 45)
  - misc. notes on books and articles (Box 56, Folder 46-47)
- Writings of Bruno de Finetti, Series V; 3 linear feet (5 boxes, 1 carton)
  These booklets, pamphlets, reprints, and manuscripts are arranged alphabetically by title. The date is noted where possible. Some articles by other Italian authors are also filed in this series. They have been arranged alphabetically by author in a separate section. Hardcover books by de Finetti have been placed together at the end of the series.
  - "The Ability of Different Response and Scoring Methods to Discriminate Levels of Partial Knowledge on a Test Item" (incomplete), 1964? (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - "Aggiunta alla nota sull 'assiomatica della probabilità", 1951 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - "Alcune osservazioni in tema di 'suddivisione casuale'", 1964 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - "The Bayesian Approach to the Rejection of Outliers" (summary), 1960 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - "Calcolo delle probabilità--Problemi deterrninati e indeterminati nel calcolo delle probabilità", 1930 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - "Calcolo delle probabilità--Sulla probabilità di valori e eccezionali per una legge di incrementi aleatori", 1929 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - "Calcolo delle probabilità--Sulle funzioni a incremento alea", 1929 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - "Cenni introduttivi e conclusivi sulle calcolatrici elettroniche e la elaborazione dei dati", 1962 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - "La matematica nelle applicazioni economiche", 1962 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - "Come si enunciano i primi teoremi dell'Analisi svincolandosi dall' ipotesi della derivabilità", 1943 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - "Commentaires sur l'essai 'futuribles' sur la decision", 1962 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - "La compensazione tra rischi eterogenei", 1954 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - "Concetti sul comportamento induttivo' illustrati su di un esempio", 1954 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - "Conferenze sulle probabilità e l'assicurazione", 1950 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - "Dans quel sens la théorie de la décision est-elle et doit-elle être 'normative'", 1959 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - "La décision dans des conditions d'incertitude", 1963 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - "La decision et les probabilités", 1963 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - "La decisione nel'incertezza", 1963 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - "Sul divario tra valutizioni di probabilità per operazioni assicurative nei due sensi", 1963 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - "Does It Make Sense to Speak of 'Good Probability Appraisers'?", 1961 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - "Econometristi allo spettroscopio", 1965 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - "Esigenze nuove, programmi da rinnovare", 1962 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - "Esperienza e teoria nell'elaborazione e nell'applicazione di una dottrina scientifica", 1956 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - "Expérience et théorie dans l'élaboration et dans l'application d'une doctrine scientifique", 1951 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - "Une façon d'introduire la notion de 'mesure,' particulièrement convenable pour la théorie des probabilités", 1954 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - "Foundations of Probability", 1956 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - "La funzione vivificatrice della matematica", 1949 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - "Gli eventi equivalenti e il caso degenere", 1952 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - "Insegnamento di Materie scientifiche nella Scuola media unica e preparazione degli insegnanti", 1964 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - "Intervento al convegno I. R. I. i sistemi aziendali avanzati", 1963 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Introduction to "The Art of Guessing", 1970 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - "L'adozione della concezione soggetti vistica come condizione necessaria e sufficiente per dissipare secolari pseudoproblemi", 1967 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - "L'apporto della matematica alla comprensione dei problemi economice", 1965/1966 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - "L'apporto della matematica nell'evoluzione del pensiero economico", 1963 (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - "L'apprendimento della matematica", 1969 (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - "Le leggi differenziali e la rinunzia al determinismo", 1931 (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - "L'esattezza nella contabilità aziendale", 1948 (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - "L'informazione, il ragionamento, l'inconscio nei rapporti con la previsione", 1957 (Box 58, Folder 37)
  - "L'intreccio reassicurativo", 1958 (Box 58, Folder 38)
  - "Su un'impostazione alternative della teoria colletiva del rischio", 1958 (Box 58, Folder 38)
  - "La 'logica del plausibile' secondo la concezione di Polya", 1951 (Box 58, Folder 39)
  - "L'opera di Abraham Wald e l'assestamento concettuale della statistica matematica moderna", 1951 (Box 58, Folder 40)
  - "Machine 'che pensano' (e che fanno pensare)", 1952 (Box 58, Folder 41)
  - "La matematica e il profano", 1965 (Box 58, Folder 42)
  - "La matematica moderna nell 'insegnamento secondario", 1968 (Box 58, Folder 43)
  - "La matematica nelle concezioni e nelle applicazione statistiche", 1943 (Box 58, Folder 44)
  - "Media di decisioni e media di opinioni", 1953 (Box 58, Folder 45)
  - "Methods for Discriminating Levels of Partial Knowledge Concerning a Test Item", 1965 (Box 58, Folder 46)
  - "Sul modo di scegliere le probabilità iniziali", 1962 (Box 58, Folder 47)
  - "La notion de 'distribution d'opinions' comme base d'un essai d'interprétation de la statistique", 1952 (Box 58, Folder 48)
  - "La notion de 'horizon bayesien'", 1954 (Box 58, Folder 49)
  - "Sulla nozione de 'dispersione' per distribuzioni a più dimensioni", 1953 (Box 58, Folder 50)
  - "La nozione di evento", 1952 (Box 58, Folder 51)
  - "Sul numero de elementi al di là dell' ultimo osservato", 1957 (Box 58, Folder 52)
  - "On Some Conventions That Seem Useful", 1969 (Box 58, Folder 53)
  - "Opportunità e limiti della utilizzazione collettiva di mezzi meccanografici", 1954 (Box 58, Folder 54)
  - "Posizione e compiti della scienza dell' amministrazione in un mondo irretito e vessato dalle complicazioni inutili", 1957 (Box 59, Folder 55)
  - "Sulla preferibilità", 1952 (Box 59, Folder 56)
  - "La prévision: ses lois logiques, ses sources subjectives", 1935-1936 (Box 59, Folder 57)
  - "La prevision: ses lois logiques, ses sources subjectives", 1935-1936 (Box 59, Folder 58)
  - "Probabilità composte e teoria delle decisioni", 1964 (Box 59, Folder 59)
  - "La probabilità e le scienze sociali", 1955 (Box 59, Folder 60)
  - "La probabilità: guida nel pensare e nell'agire", 1965 (Box 59, Folder 61)
  - Les Probabilités nulles, 1936 (Box 59, Folder 62)
  - "Probability, Philosophy and Interpretation", 1963 (Box 59, Folder 63)
  - "Probability: the Subjectivistic Approach", 1967 (Box 59, Folder 64)
  - "Probability, Statistics, and Induction" (copy one), 1968 (Box 59, Folder 65)
  - "Probability, Statistics, and Induction" (copy two), 1968 (Box 59, Folder 66)
  - "Probability, Statistics, and Induction" (notes) (Box 59, Folder 67)
  - "Probability, Statistics, and Induction" (rough draft), 1968 (Box 59, Folder 68)
  - Les problèmes Psychologiques sur les probabilités subjectives, 1955 (Box 60, Folder 69)
  - "Un procedimento per la revisione del calcolo delle riserve matematiche", 1950 (Box 60, Folder 70)
  - "Programmi e criteri per l'insegnamento della matematica alla luce delle diverse esigenze", 1965 (Box 60, Folder 71)
  - "Progressi e prospettive nel campo delle calculatrici elettroniche", 1953 (Box 60, Folder 72)
  - "A proposito di una ricera sull'andamento della mortalità nelle età senili", 1953 (Box 60, Folder 73)
  - "Sulla proprietà conglomerativa delle probabilità subordinate", 1930 (Box 60, Folder 74)
  - "Sulla proseguibilità di processi aleatori scambiabili", 1969 (Box 60, Folder 75)
  - "Punti di vista: D. van Dantzig", 1941 (Box 60, Folder 76)
  - "Recent Suggestions for the Reconciliation of Theories of Probability", 1951 (Box 60, Folder 77)
  - "Remore e freni sul cammino della scienza", 1964 (Box 60, Folder 78)
  - review of R. Carnap's Logical Foundations of Probability, 1951 (Box 60, Folder 79)
  - review of Selected Papers of Richard von Mises, 1964 (Box 60, Folder 80)
  - "Riflessioni attuali sulla teoria dei giochi", 1963? (Box 60, Folder 81)
  - Rôle de la 'théorie des jeux' dans l'économie, et rôle des probabilités personnelles dans la théorie des jeux, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 82)
  - "Il 'Saper Verdere' in matematica", 1967 (Box 60, Folder 83)
  - "Scatenare l'intelligenza, non soffocarla", undated (Box 60, Folder 84)
  - "La scienza e la lotta contro l'incertezza", 1962 (Box 60, Folder 85)
  - "Spazi astratti metrici", 1930 (Box 60, Folder 86)
  - "Sulle stratificazioni convesse", 1949 (Box 60, Folder 87)
  - "La struttura delle distribuzioni in un insiem astratto gualiasi", 1955 (Box 60, Folder 88)
  - "Subjective or Objective Probability: Is the Dispute Undecidable?", 1971 (Box 60, Folder 89)
  - "Sulla suddivisione casuale di un intervallo: spunti per riflessioni", 1967 (Box 60, Folder 90)
  - "Sull'applicazione dei numeri normali delle tariffe ferroviarie", 1949 (Box 60, Folder 91)
  - "Sull'impostazione assiomatica del calcolo delle probabilità", 1949 (Box 60, Folder 92)
  - "Sull'opportunità di perfezionamenti e di estensione de funzioni dei Servizi anagrafici", 1963 (Box 60, Folder 93)
  - Sur l'emploi d'une base technique générale pour les risques tares, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 94)
  - "Sviluppo della popolazione e sicurezza sociale", 1956 (Box 60, Folder 95)
  - "La tecnica organizzativa nelle pubbliche amministrazioni in una recente pubblicazione", 1954 (Box 60, Folder 96)
  - "Sulla teoria astratta della misura e dell'integrazione", 1955 (Box 60, Folder 97)
  - "La teoria dei giochi", 1963 (Box 60, Folder 98)
  - "Teoria dei valori estremi e sua applicazione ai problemi dell'assicurazione", 1963 (Box 60, Folder 99)
  - "Sulla teoria della credibilità", 1964 (Box 60, Folder 100)
  - "Teoria delle decisioni e recera operativa", 1961 (Box 60, Folder 101)
  - "Trasformazioni di numeri aleatori atte a far coincidere distribuzioni diverse", 1953 (Box 60, Folder 102)
  - "The True SP Problem (Subjective Probability Problem) Versus Various More or Less Related Side Problems", 1969 (Box 60, Folder 103)
  - "Una legge riguardante l'estinzione nei processi de eliminazione", 1953 (Box 60, Folder 104)
  - "Unità e metodo delle ricerche e degli studi relative alle applicazioni della scienza dell'organizzazione della pubblica amministrazione", 1955 (Box 60, Folder 105)
  - "Verso l'era elettronica nell'assicurazione?", 1956 (Box 60, Folder 106)
  - "Le vrai et le probable", 1948 (Box 60, Folder 107)
  - dissertation of G. Dell'Era (student of De Finetti) (Box 61, Folder 108)
  - dissertation of C. Mirella (student of De Finetti) (Box 61, Folder 109)
  - misc. pamphlets by various Italian authors (Baldessari-Bruno) (Box 61, Folder 110)
  - misc. pamphlets by various Italian authors (Camatini--De Carolis) (Box 61, Folder 111)
  - misc. pamphlets by various Italian authors (De Lucia--Fortunati) (Box 61, Folder 112)
  - misc. pamphlets by various Italian authors (Gabrielle--Salvemini) (Box 61, Folder 113)
  - Box 62 contains copies of the following books by Bruno de Finetti:
    - Economia delle assicurazioni (with F. Emanuelli), 1967 (Box 62)
    - Lezioni di matematica attuariale, 1956-1957 (Box 62)
    - Lezioni di matematica finanziaria, 1955-1956 (Box 62)
    - La matematica per le applicazioni economiche (with F. Minasola), 1961 (Box 62)
    - Matematica logico intuitiva, 1957 (Box 62)
    - Un matematico e l'economia, 1969 (Box 62)
    - Seminari di matematica finanziaria e attuariale, 1955, 1957 (Box 62)
    - Teoria delle probabilità, vols. 1 and 2, 1970 (Box 62)
    - Teoria delle Probabilità, typed and annotated, inscribed to Tjalling C. Koopmans. Add 12/8/83, 1964 (Box 62)
- Book File, Series VI; 4 linear feet (4 cartons)
  Boxes 66A, 66B, and 66C were previously restricted. The restriction was lifted as of May 30, 1993.
  The books in this series have been arranged alphabetically by author or editor. An asterisk before the author's name in the following list means that there is correspondence with the author in the CORRESPONDENCE series.
  - Box 63 contains copies of the following books:
    - Archer, S. H. and *D'Ambrosio, C. A. The Theory of Business Finance: A Book of Readings (Box 63)
    - Bartlett, M. S. An Introduction to Stochastic Processes (Box 63)
    - (*) Blackwell, D. and Girshick, M. A. Theory of Games and Statistical Decisions (Box 63)
    - (*) Bochner, S. Harmonic Analysis and the Theory of Probability (Box 63)
    - (*) Breiman, L. Probability and Stochastic Processes (Box 63)
    - Cantelli, F. P. Alcune memorie (Box 63)
    - Clark, C. E. An Introduction to Statistics (Box 63)
    - (*) Cox, R. T. The Algebra of Probable Inference (Box 63)
    - Daboni, L. Calcolo delle probabilità ed elementi di statistica (Box 63)
    - Dixon, W. J. and Massey, F. J. Introduction to Statistical Analysis (Box 63)
    - Doob, J. L. Stochastic Processes (Box 63)
    - Eisenhart, C. and others. Selected Techniques of Statistical Analysis (Box 63)
  - Box 64 contains copies of the following books:
    - Fegiz, P. L. Il volto sconosciuto dell'Italia (Box 64)
    - (*) Feller, W. An Introduction to Probability Theory and Its Application, volumes 1 and 2 (Box 64)
    - (*) Fishburn, P. Utility Theory for Decision Making (Box 64)
    - (*) Fisher, R. A. The Design of Experiments (Box 64)
    - (*) Fisher, R. A. Statistical Methods and Scientific Inference (Box 64)
    - (*) Fisher, R. A. Statistical Methods for Research Workers (Box 64)
    - *Fraser, D. A. S. Nonparametric Methods in Statistics (Box 64)
    - Gini, C. Il sesso (Box 64)
    - Gini, C. Corso di statistica (Box 64)
  - Box 65 contains copies of the following books:
    - Gini, C. Variabilità e concentrazione (Box 65)
    - (*) Good, I. J. The Estimation of Probabilities (Box 65)
    - (*) Good, I. J. Probability and the Weighing of Evidence (Box 65)
    - (*) Halmos, P. R. Measure Theory (Box 65)
    - Hamilton, E. J. and others. Landmarks in Political Economy (Box 65)
    - Jaynes, E. T. Probability Theory in Science and Engineering (Box 65)
    - (*) Jeffrey, R. C. The Logic of Decision (Box 65)
    - (*) Jeffreys, H. Theory of Probability (Box 65)
    - (*) Kempthorne, O. The Design and Analysis of Experiments (Box 65)
    - (*) Kyburg, H. E. and Smokler, H. E. Studies in Subjective Probability (Box 65)
    - (*) Lehmann, E. L. Testing Statistical Hypotheses (Box 65)
    - Lucas, J. R. The Concept of Probability (Box 65)
    - (*) Luce, R. Duncan. Individual Choice Behavior (Box 65)
    - (*) Machol, R. E. and Gray, P. Recent Developments in Information and Decision Processes (Box 65)
  - Box 66 contains copies of the following books:
    - Moisil, G. C. Essais sur les logiques non chrysippiennes (Box 66)
    - Munroe, M. E. Theory of Probability (Box 66)
    - (*) Newman, P. The Theory of Exchange (Box 66)
    - Pompilj, G. and *Dall'Aglio, G. Piano degli esperimenti (Box 66)
    - Prontuari - I tavole (Box 66)
    - Prontuari - II complementi (Box 66)
    - (*) Raiffa, H. and *Schlaifer, R. Applied Statistical Decision Theory (Box 66)
    - Wald, A. Statistical Decision Functions (Box 66)
    - (*) Wallis, W. A. and *Roberts, H. V. Statistics: A New Approach (Box 66)
    - (*) Watts, D. G. The Future of Statistics (Box 66)
    - Zygmund, A. Trigonometrical Series (Box 66)
- Additions
  NOTE: Correspondence of L. J. Savage and William Henry Kruskal, 1966-1970, added to Box 19, folders 466 and 467.
  1 folder
  - Addition 1977 June
    "On Rereading R. A. Fisher," an article published in The Annals of Statistics, vol. 4, no. 3, 1976, was edited for publication by John W. Pratt from the lecture, "On Rereading Fisher," given by Leonard A. Savage as the R. A. Fisher Memorial Lecture, at the A.S.A. Meeting, Detroit, Michigan, on December 29, 1970.
    - "On Rereading R. A. Fisher," R. A. Fisher Memorial Lecture, A.S.A. Meeting, Detroit, Michigan, tape, 1970 December 29 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Transcript of tape of L. J. Savage's Fisher Memorial Lecture, typescript draft with corrections, undated (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Transcript of tape of L. J. Savage's Fisher Memorial Lecture, typescript, undated (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Typescript of lecture with amendations by John W. Pratt, [1974 Dec] (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Typescript draft of the article with amendations, undated (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Typescript draft of the published article with corrections, [1974 Dec] (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Comments by:
      - B. Efron, undated (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Churchill Eisenhart, undated (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Brunode Finetti, 1975 April 22 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - D.A.S. Fraser, undated (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - V.P. Godambe, undated (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - I.J. Good, 1975 March 28 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - O. Kempthorne, undated (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Stephen M. Stigler, undated (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - I. Richard Savage, 1975 February 8 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - [anonymous] not published, 1975 February 8 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Reprint from The Annals of Statistics, Vol. 4, No. 3, 1976 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - R. A. Fisher, Contributions to Mathematical Statistics, bound volume, New York: John Wiley & Sons, Inc., 1950 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Addition 1976 Mar
    - "Personal Probabilities of Probabilities" by Jacob Marchak and others. Reprint no. 135, 1974 May (Box 68)
    - Copy of review of 2nd edition of The Foundations of Statistics, undated (Box 68)
  - Addition 1976 May 21
    - Inequalities for Stochastic Processes: How to Gamble If You Must, by Lester E. Dubins and Leonard J. Savage., 1976 (Box 68)
  - Addition 1976 Jun 8
    - Typescript "Non Parametric and Robust Aspects of Bayesian Statistical Analysis" by I. Richard Savage and related correspondence, 1960 December (Box 68)
  - Addition 1977 Sep 2
    - ALS 1972 Feb 24 Lawrence Seltzer to Mr. & Mrs. Louis Savage (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - xerox clipping, article by Charles Holcomb 'Bet the Whole $100' (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - inauguration program, W. Allen Wallis as President of the University of Rochester, 1963 May 17 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - inaugural dinner program, W. Allen Wallis, University of Rochester, 1963 May 16 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - memorial service program, Leonard Jimmie Savage, Dwight Memorial Chapel, Yale University, 1972 March 18 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Advance Program for the 50th Annual Meeting, American Educational Research Association, 1966 February 17-19 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - official copy of a petition by Leonard Jimmie Savage before Circuit Court for the County of Wayne, State of Michigan, for proof of identity (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - 8" x 10" black and white photograph including President Eisenhower, Rochester University President Wallis, and L. J. Savage (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - page from Rochester Democrat Chronicle showing above photograph reproduced on the front page, 1963 May 18 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - signed carbon copy of TL 1971 Nov 23 James W. Walker to Mrs. Jean Strickland Savage and Family (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Yale News Bureau release announcing the death of L. J. Savage, 3 copies, 1971 November 2 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - xerox copies of letters and notes to Richard Savage, 13 items, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - typed copy of entry for Leonard Jimmie Savage in Who's Who in America, vol. 36, 1970-1971 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - 8/82 Add: Booklet, correspondence, publications, and clippings (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - 11/82 Add: Correspondence between L. J. Savage and R. A. Fischer (See preliminary inventory sheet), 1952-1958 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - photostatic copies of the entries of L. J. Savage in American Men of Science, 9th, 11th edition (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - article by George A. W. Boehm, "The Science of Being Almost Certain," Fortune, 1964 February (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - clippings, death notices and obituaries of L. J. Savage from various papers, 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - receipts for use of classified military documents used by L. J. Savage during WWII, 1946 May 21 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - letters of condolence on the death of L. J. Savage to Richard and Louis Savage, originals and some xerox copies, 9 items, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 5)